♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
["Mr. Tailor" playing]
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
How was your date with Cathy?
We're together now!
What? You thought I got rejected?
This wouldn't have happened without you.
[Cathy] Gavsy!
Can you take a video of me
while I donate blood?
[Gavin] Sure, let's go.
Let's eat at the lechon restaurant
at the mall.
[Tonet] That's Audrey's, huh.
Ah, sir! Can we follow that car?
Where's the man who caught the thief
who stole my phone yesterday?
- That was me.
- [Denden] It wasn't you.
It was the handsome curly-haired guy.
I saw that Wonderkids is showing now!
What do you think?
- G! I want that--
- I actually like that more.
Let's buy tickets.
We don't have tickets yet!
- [Atoy] Looks like it's starting.
- [Tonet] Is Audrey here?
I'll knock on her door.
Uh, what does she want?
[in English] Are you saying that Janine
is not really their child?
Let's retest to be sure.
She doesn't need to do that,
and she doesn't need to listen to you.
[in English] Please, just leave.
Why don't you want me to talk to Audrey?
PREVIOUSLY
Are you hiding something?
Audrey, Audrey!
- [Red] Hey!
- [Tonet gasps]
[Red] Why are you pushing my wife, huh?
What's your problem? Who are you?
You're a trespasser, aren't you?
- Do you want me to kill you?
- [Tonet] Whoa! I'm leaving!
Make sure your boys follow that woman.
Don't let her get close to Atoy.
[Mongki] What's our plan for her, boss?
We'll exploit her.
If she resists…
you know what to do.
[music fades]
- Daddy, let's run.
- We'll be late…
Oh, I'll get it. I'll come back for you.
[suspicious music playing]
Ibyang, your shoelace!
Fix it, quick!
[Ibyang grunts]
There.
[music fades]
[tense music playing]
Where are they?
[suave theme music playing]
[motorcycle revving]
[sewing machine whirring]
[scratches]
[snipping]
[sewing machine clacking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshots]
[gunshots]
[clicking]
[snipping]
[electronic blipping]
- [pensive music playing]
- [old woman] Your misfortune
will come in threes!
If not you, then maybe
the one you love.
[phone blips]
Hello, Tonet?
Oh, brother? Oh,
I'm on my way to the mall.
Seems you've been on your way for a while.
Uh, maybe… you should just go home first?
So… it's safe.
I'm already on my way. It's fine, brother.
I'm on my way.
Let's just chat at the restaurant.
And I have a lot to tell you.
[Tonet] I don't have anyone to talk to.
I can't tell Atoy.
What's it about?
Okay, okay. Let's just meet
at the restaurant.
Yes, okay.
No problem, love--
[line beeping]
Hello?
- Tonet. Hello?
- [line beeping]
[tense music playing]
Sir, sir, do you have a charger?
[driver] I don't, ma'am.
[softly] I'm giving you one star.
[music swells]
[music fades]
Oh, where's Ibyang?
Um, Ibyang? I don't know.
- She was just behind me earlier.
- [indistinct]
What do you mean you don't know?
Where did she go?
- Um…
- [Atoy] Huh?
[suspicious music playing]
You were just together earlier.
Where's Ibyang?
[stammering]
Miss, uh…
Uh, cancel.
- We're not going to watch the movie.
- Wait--
I thought we're going to watch a movie?
How can we,
if you don't know where Ibyang is?
We'll look for her.
Miss, sorry, but we'll just try
to come back.
Uh, Daddy, maybe we should
go to the first floor.
Maybe she stayed there.
- [in English] First floor?
- First floor…
- [Janine] Yes.
- [Atoy] Come on…
[music fades]
BE A HERO
DONATE BLOOD TODAY
[T-Bak chuckles]
- Hey.
- [quirky sting]
Karla, let's play basketball later.
Let's bet on it!
You guys go ahead.
Oh? Why do you look so down?
Did they take a lot of blood
from you earlier?
‪[quirky sting]
You know, the cure
for your blood loss is here! [chuckles]
- Huh?
- [both] Gavin!
[elated sound]
- [giggles]
- [stammers]
Stop it already.
He's with Cathy now. Let them be together.
- Huh?
- What?
- Jealous.
- What do you mean?
[pensive music playing]
Uh, together.
Through thick and thin.
[chuckles] Karla, we're not
getting married yet.
But you know what?
[in English] I really need to thank you.
You convinced me
to give Gavin a second chance.
He's so fun to be with, right?
And so humble, just like you said.
So, I said yes to him!
[T-Bak] What?
You're Gavin's girlfriend?
[both] Really?
[in English] Karla, here's the thing.
I know you're close to Gavsy, my babe.
But since we're together now,
I wouldn't really feel
too comfortable with him getting
too close to other girls.
[in English] And that includes you.
[in English] So, I hope you understand.
They're just friends.
And also, she--
So arrogant.
[in English] Okay.
That's not a problem.
[in English] Okay, thanks. Bye!
[melancholic music playing]
She's so fussy.
[T-Bak] Acting like she's special.
[ominous music playing]
- [line ringing]
- [tense music playing]
Boss.
Roger, Mongki said you're here.
We're at Terrazza Mall.
Looks like she's meeting someone here.
[Red] We're here too.
Boss,
the picture you showed me, Atoy
and your niece are here.
Don't show yourself to them.
But make sure
Tonet doesn't see them.
[man] What?
Where is she?
Um… Daddy, where are we going?
The administration office.
Let's ask for help.
So they can help us look for Ibyang.
Um, Daddy, I'll just go to the CR first.
[pensive music playing]
All right, all right. I'll wait for you.
[tense music playing]
- [music fades]
- [inaudible]
♪ Don't get ahead ♪
♪ Of the feelings ♪
♪ Of my heart ♪
♪ That's no stranger to this… ♪
Karla, are you okay?
I'm fine.
["Sa Wala" by Wickermoss
with Weth Macam playing]
You know, you don't have to pretend.
If you're not okay, then you're not.
If you don't want to share yet,
I won't force you.
♪ Not that ♪
♪ I'm thinking badly ♪
♪ There are many like you… ♪
But can I hug you?
♪ What has passed and carried ♪
♪ Hard to let go ♪
♪ I don't want games… ♪
I think I know why you're crying.
It's Gavin, isn't it?
Sis Ame, he's with Cathy now.
What?
He beat Tonet and me
in having a relationship.
Too bad Tonet isn't here.
Then both of us could give you
advice as your sisters.
I've been texting her nonstop.
She's not replying.
Where is she?
Well, she was looking for Atoy.
Maybe they're together now.
♪ Forcing us to have something together ♪
♪ If it's only for nothing… ♪
Let it go.
[music fades]
[ominous music playing]
Mmm, Janine!
You're with Atoy?
[Janine] No.
Then who are you with?
None of your business.
Janine!
- [tense music playing]
- [Tonet] Oh.
Oh, sorry--
Oh, my. Sorry.
Sorry, sorry.
[woman] Where are you even going?
[in English] You're so careless!
[Tonet] Sorry, sorry.
Janine!
Janine. Where is that child?
So-sorry.
That kid is really stubborn.
Janine!
[music fades]
Hey! Ibyang!
Oh? Brother Emerson!
What are you doing here?
You're too young to be wandering around.
Uh, I'm with Tatoy and Janine.
- Ah.
- We were going to watch a movie,
but I got left behind.
- [Emerson] Oh?
- I asked the ticket seller.
They said they didn't go inside.
Oh, so where did they go?
I'm looking for them too.
Ah. Let's call Atoy.
He left his phone at the shop.
Is that so?
[suspicious music playing]
Oh, uh, mmm.
All right, let's go.
- Let's look for them.
- Okay.
[Emerson] Mmm.
[music fades]
- [soft rock music playing]
- Psst. Is it delicious?
This looks delicious. This is delicious.
Hold it. Bring it here.
Ah! Psst! Psst.
Ah… No, no.
- [man] Bro, selfie…
- Oh, let's take a selfie.
Oh, se-sel…
[lively chatter]
There. That's a good one. A good shot.
- [lively chatter]
- [camera shutter snaps]
[teenagers cheer]
You're cool, bro!
[ominous music playing]
- Atoy!
- [dramatic sting]
Atoy!
- Where are you going?
- You followed me?
Yes.
[foreboding music playing]
So come with me…
unless you want me to put
a bullet through you.
Come on. Let's have a date.
‪[dramatic stinging]
[Red] Just walk normally.
- [dramatic sting]
- I was right.
Janine is a fake child,
and you and Martina know it.
You wouldn't do this to me if I was wrong.
- Shut up.
- [tense music playing]
Why did you have to use another child
to pretend she's her daughter, huh?
What did you do-- [grunts]
Psst! I said shut up! Huh?
Even if you escape from me here,
I'll find you.
I'll still kill you.
I'll kill your whole family too.
Do you understand?
‪-[dramatic sting]
‪-[gasps]
- Come on!
- [dramatic sting]
Let's just page Atoy at the mall office.
He's probably looking for you too.
Where's the office?
I don't know. Let's just find it.
[pensive music playing]
- [thumps]
- Hey!
Are you okay? Hey!
Why? What's wrong?
You weren't looking!
You bumped into the kid!
Be thankful I have work.
If not, I'd beat you up.
Oh, better get to work then!
He thinks we're scared of him?
[chuckles]
Go to work, or you'll be late!
- [exhales]
- Brother Emerson, stop fighting!
Let's go!
Why did you stop me just now?
I almost got hit by him.
You should've told me earlier.
You weren't looking.
[chuckles]
[music fades]
[line rings]
Martina, tell Roger.
I'm with Tonet.
Let's go to the parking lot, okay?
Come on.
[rousing music playing]
[quivering breath]
[gasping and panicking]
- [Red] Don't touch her, don't touch her!
- [woman, indistinct]
- [Red] Leave her! Leave her!
- [woman] What are you doing?
[Red] Leave her! No, no!
Hands off, hands off!
Ah, I-- I'll take her.
I'll bring her to the hospital.
[music fades]
- [Atoy] Ibyang!
- There she is!
[Emerson] Finally!
- Oh my!
- What's wrong with you?
Where did you go? Hmm?
We've been looking for you!
Hmm?
We didn't get to watch the movie.
So annoying.
I just tied my shoelace.
Then suddenly, you were gone.
Good thing Brother Emerson was here.
- Bro, thanks.
- [in English] Okay, no prob!
But I'll go ahead, bro,
because I have a lechon date with Tonet.
- [smirks]
- Lechon?
- Really, huh? Lechon?
- Yes!
Because it has sentimental value for us.
Since we were kids in Cebu.
Even though there's plenty there,
I couldn't afford it.
So, I promised her,
when I become successful,
I'd treat her to lechon,
and today's that day.
It's a bit pricey
at the restaurant I reserved.
But luckily, I have…
a discount voucher!
[giggles]
If you're successful,
why do you still need a voucher?
Doesn't using a voucher mean
you have no money?
If you have no money,
you're not successful.
That's common sense.
Mmm… [giggles]
You're really cute!
Money isn't the only measure of success.
Hmm? Okay? Remember that.
[mellow music playing]
[Emerson mutters]
So?
Oh, Atoy-- Ouch.
- Hey.
- Ouch, ouch!
What was that?
What-- Hey!
- [soft rock music playing]
- [Emerson groans]
Wait, wait, wait. Ouch, it hurts.
- Stop that thief!
- [Emerson] Huh?
[guard] There's a thief!
- A th-thief?
- He's a thief!
A thief?
Wait, my wallet?
- [guard] Chase him, chase him.
- [gasps]
My wallet was stolen, Atoy.
Chase him!
- Retrieve my wallet!
- Huh? Why me?
It can't be Ibyang! Go on. It's there--
- Our voucher's in there!
- Okay, okay! The kids!
I'll handle it!
Our lechon voucher is in there!
[sighs]
Come on? Come on, stop it. Stand up!
[soft rock music playing]
Ah, sir, sir, sir!
[Tonet gasping]
Help me! That's a bad man!
He wants to kill me!
No-- Gun? He has a gun hidden behind him!
No! I don't have a gun!
What are you saying? I don't have a gun!
[gasps] Sir, he's lying!
Help me!
Wait, uh, ma--
Sir, she's the one who pretended
to be sick earlier?
Then I'm the bad one?
She's probably the bad one, right?
[woman] This woman was just pretending.
Uh, I think she's a thief!
Now she's just pretending
to be sick to escape.
Huh? I didn't do anything.
Really, I didn't…
[Red] Come here! She's the bad person!
[Tonet] He's the bad one!
- Not me. Not--
- [Tonet] Don't--
- [guard] What happened here?
- No, no. Uh…
Uh, she's a thief. A thief.
Pretending to be sick, to evade me!
[woman 1] So, you're a thief, miss!
- Yes!
- Are you part of a gang?
[tense music playing]
[man] Move aside!
[soft rock music playing]
[man] Oh, move!
[music swells]
My fall was terrible. Ouch, ouch.
[groans]
My day is even worse.
I'm exhausted from walking around.
It was supposed
to be bonding time with Daddy,
but we ended up everywhere.
Oh my.
So annoying.
[scoffs]
You know, you…
You complain all the time.
That attitude isn't good, young girl.
It should've been just Daddy and me.
Sorry if your day got ruined
because of me.
But Tatoy said the three of us
should be together.
[pensive music playing]
Let it go, let it go.
I won't give her any lechon.
She won't get any lechon from me.
It hurts.
[sighs]
Brother Emerson, maybe
you should go to the clinic?
You might have a fracture.
No, it's fine. I can handle it.
Good thing this happened to me.
Maybe this is the third misfortune
the old woman told me about earlier.
At least it happened to me.
Not to Tonet.
Why me? Sir, he's the bad person!
Sir, not me!
[Tonet] Why me?
- He's the bad person!
- Arrest that woman!
She stole my cellphone!
- See?
- [guard] Come here!
I'm not a thief!
- They're a couple!
- Come on!
They're just framing me!
- They want to kill me--
- [Red] Sir, no-- No--
We're not a couple. We're just concerned.
It would be better, sir, um…
if we take her. We'll take care of her.
She should be with the police.
- Right?
- Let's go, let's go!
- [Tonet shrieks]
- [guard gasps]
[tense music playing]
You're too slow!
[music swells]
[action music playing]
[gasping]
[Tonet, in English] Excuse me.
[Tonet gasping]
- [Tonet squealing]
- [clamoring]
[Tonet shrieks]
[screaming]
[gasps]
[soft rock music playing]
[Red] Move aside!
Move aside. Move aside!
Get out of the way!
Where are you going?
[dramatic stinging]
- [Red] Hey! Where are you going?
- [guard shouts]
- [music fades]
- [panting]
‪[dramatic stinging]
[Atoy] You bastard.
You really made me chase you.
Give me my friend's wallet.
[pants]
This wallet?
Give it.
So, this is all of it? This wallet!
Here, take it!
Son of a--
Keep the money. The voucher.
I need the voucher. It's important to him.
Give it back.
This?
You have to take it from me.
I'm not giving it back
without something in return.
[music fades]
Maybe you got something for me?
- Like what?
- Anything, in exchange for this.
The money isn't enough.
[tense music playing]
Give me your wallet instead.
Your friend's money isn't enough.
Right, boys?
- [teenagers] Yes, it's not enough!
- Not at all!
[dramatic sting]
[car door clicks shut]
Uh, bros…
Uh, calm down.
Calm down and relax.
All I'm asking for is that voucher.
Huh? The voucher is all I want.
You can have the money.
Give me your wallet first.
- My wallet?
- Yes. In exchange for this.
[ominous music playing]
Right, boys? The money
isn't enough for us!
[teenagers] Yes!
Relax. Okay, okay, wait.
Just give me that. And I'll give you this.
This? Okay.
- We'll exchange, huh.
- [music fades]
[grunting and groaning]
- [thumping]
- [grunting]
- [weapons swooshing]
- [grunting and groaning]
[thumping]
[music fades]
[panting]
Oh, Lord. Thank you, Lord.
Good thing I escaped. [panting]
[panting]
[ominous music playing]
Oh, thank you, Lord. I escaped.
[panting continues]
[Martina, in English]
That's what you think.
[rousing music playing]
[electronic blipping]
Leave me alone!
I already have a quiet life!
- [clangs]
- [grunting]
UP NEXT
[clangs]
- [clinks]
- What is that?
[Atoy] This belongs to Tonet.
Have you seen Tonet?
Atoy beat me to it.
[Atoy] Let's get out of here.
This place looks dangerous.
[Ibyang] Tatoy, something's moving…
Maybe a kitten!
♪ Oh, Mr. Tailor ♪
♪ Holding the scissors ♪
♪ One cut, and it's settled ♪
♪ Fix it ♪
Subtitle translation by: Rachel C. Arias